<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reading on Wei Wang&#39;s Space</title>
    <link>https://weiwangblog.github.io/tags/reading/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reading on Wei Wang&#39;s Space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 23:57:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://weiwangblog.github.io/tags/reading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Ioannidis on Results of Covid-19 Studies</title>
      <link>https://weiwangblog.github.io/posts/dr-dot-ioannidis-on-results-of-coronacirus-studies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 23:57:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weiwangblog.github.io/posts/dr-dot-ioannidis-on-results-of-coronacirus-studies/</guid>
      <description>约翰·A·约阿尼迪斯（John P. A. Ioannidis）是一名希腊裔美国医师，科学家和作家，为循证医学，流行病学和临床研究做出了贡献。 约阿尼迪斯研究科学研究本身，主要研究临床医学和社会科学的元研究。他是C.F. 雷恩堡疾病预防主席，医学教授，专攻流行病学和人群健康，以及（由礼貌提供）生物医学数据科学和统计学； 斯坦福大学元研究创新中心（METRICS）联合主任。
这是他对加州Santa Clara冠状病毒抽样调查对数据研究后发表对看法。当然，主流媒体并不报道。
Dr. Ioannidis on Results of Coronacirus Studies   Transcript This study aimed to generate an estimate of how many people in Santa Clara County have been infected with a virus. And the way to find out is to try to see whether they have developed antibodies to SARS Covid-19.
We realize that the number of infected people is somewhere between 50 and 85 times more compared to what we thought compared to what had been documented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>自免疫病学习报告</title>
      <link>https://weiwangblog.github.io/posts/autoimmune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 21:31:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weiwangblog.github.io/posts/autoimmune/</guid>
      <description>背景  &amp;ldquo;Reports that say that something hasn&amp;rsquo;t happened are always interesting to me, because as we know, there are known knowns; there are things we know we know. We also know there are known unknowns; that is to say we know there are some things we do not know. But there are also unknown unknowns – the ones we don&amp;rsquo;t know we don&amp;rsquo;t know. And if one looks throughout the history of our country and other free countries, it is the latter category that tend to be the difficult ones.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>